export const questionsData = [
  {
    question: "1. How can I contact you?",
    answer:
      "You can reach me through the contact form on my website. I'll get back to you as soon as possible.",
  },
  {
    question: "2. What services do you offer?",
    answer:
      "I offer a range of digital services, including custom website development, responsive design, frontend and backend development, and more. Explore my Services section for details.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3. Do you have experience with Content Management Systems (CMS)?",
    answer:
      "Yes, I have experience with CMS like Strapi and a bit of WordPress. While I'm still learning, I'm committed to providing an easy and stress-free content management experience for your site.",
  },
  {
    question: "4. How do you ensure website accessibility?",
    answer:
      "Ensuring digital accessibility is a top priority for me. I use tools like Screen Readers, stay updated on accessibility guidelines, and run tests to create inclusive and user-friendly online experiences. Lately, I have been thinking about even calling Free Online Accessibility Testers so they can test the accesibility of my Site, and give me a lot of Feedback so I can improve.",
  },
  {
    question: "5. Can I update my website content myself?",
    answer:
      "Absolutely! I provide personalized training videos to empower you to manage common aspects of your website independently. From content updates to basic maintenance, I'm here to help you learn.",
  },
  {
    question: "6. What is your approach to SEO optimization?",
    answer:
      "I focus on comprehensive SEO optimization, from keyword research to on-page optimization. My goal is to strategically position your website to reach a wider audience and drive organic traffic.",
  },
  {
    question: "7. How can I view your portfolio projects?",
    answer:
      "You can explore my original projects in the Projects section of my portfolio. These projects showcase my skills in design and code, incorporating lessons learned from various learning projects.",
  },
  {
    question: "8. Do you provide ongoing support for websites?",
    answer:
      "Yes, I offer ongoing support and content updates for websites. Whether you need assistance with maintenance or have questions about your site, I'm here to help.",
  },
  {
    question: "9. How do I inquire about your services?",
    answer:
      "You can use the contact form on my website to inquire about my services. Feel free to share your project details, and I'll get back to you with more information.",
  },
  {
    question: "10. What is your process for website development?",
    answer:
      "My process includes understanding your requirements, creating visually appealing and functional designs, and ensuring seamless adaptation to various devices. I value open communication and collaboration throughout the development journey.",
  },
];
